[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "I mean, when a candidate starts telling supporters it's time for a reassessment, it's over, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Are you 100 percent confident, you, his close friend, his adviser, are you 100 percent confident that she is simply inventing a 13-year affair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Piers, I'm not 100 percent confident that when I walk out of this building that, I'm not going to get struck by lightning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Who do you believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "You know, I have no way of knowing who to believe in all of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "But are you really going to look the American public in the eye collectively as a team and say, every one of these women is a fantasist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "I mean, why wouldn't his lawyer say the same thing he's saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "If it turns out Herman Cain has been telling porky pies and has had an affair with this woman, would you then advise him to stand down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I would advise that that is a blow that would be difficult to come back from.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Why, Michael?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "You know, I just think that -- Mark.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Isn't that going to be antagonistic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "He needed to do the documentary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Do you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "I just got to say this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Will you appeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["January"], "MONEY": ["$100 million"]}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Does Conrad Murray have any money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, the judge might assess restitution in the sum of $100 million in January when we have to go back to court.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Were you expecting the worst of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Today, yes, I have been expecting the worst ever since the jury said guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "And how is Conrad today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I haven't talked with him today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "I mean, are there many doctors in Hollywood that would ever do that to somebody of Michael Jackson's stature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I think that they have to know that somewhere along the way that the whole thing's going to go off the rails.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I think it's appalling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Elizabeth Smart"]}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Of all these cases, John, which is the one that has the most significance to you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I have to say Elizabeth Smart.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Dane, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Piers, that's the introduction I wish I had every time I went home right there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "What are you at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I'm about 1.5.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Isn't that true about comedians?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "We're fragile souls, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "So why be on a medium where a load of people come on every day and say you are not funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "That's true, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "It's the ultimate kind of thing that you crave, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "How many have you literally laughed into bed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Oh, wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Not as many as you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Is that it, four?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "You can't leave it at four, because you need a football team, with at least five a side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No, because one is bound to turn out to be an A-hole.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "-- produce a whole breeding ground of young comedians and comediennes?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Boy, I don't know if I would want to catapult put them into that world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "I've always been curious, when you're a comedian and you're high profile and you're out there and you're facing audiences and stuff, how easy is it to use comedy as a mask of how you're really feeling in situations like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Yes, you definitely reach a point -- and I know that through my 20s, it was really about what I was experiencing then, just partying, being young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Is that healthy or unhealthy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I think it's what we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Do you still have days when you just bomb, when it just goes horribly wrong an, when you face that awful moment for any comedian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I think right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Seriously, did you ever get those days anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Subjects?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "What's the ambition left for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I think it's -- I made a choice a few years ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]